<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>scikit-multiflow</title><link>https://scikit-multiflow.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on scikit-multiflow</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://scikit-multiflow.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Improved base class to be introduced in release 0.3.0</title><link>https://scikit-multiflow.github.io/posts/2019-05-15-new-base-class/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scikit-multiflow.github.io/posts/2019-05-15-new-base-class/</guid><description>The upcoming release &lt;code>0.3.0&lt;/code> will introduce an improved base object class &lt;code>BaseSMKObject&lt;/code> which is consistent with &lt;code>sklearn.BaseEstimator&lt;/code>.</description></item><item><title>Conda release.</title><link>https://scikit-multiflow.github.io/posts/2019-04-11-conda/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scikit-multiflow.github.io/posts/2019-04-11-conda/</guid><description>&lt;code>scikit-multiflow&lt;/code> is now available as a package in conda-forge!</description></item><item><title>New release 0.1.0 and PyPI availability.</title><link>https://scikit-multiflow.github.io/posts/2019-01-23-v0.1.0/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scikit-multiflow.github.io/posts/2019-01-23-v0.1.0/</guid><description>The initial (minor) release 0.1.0 is now available and has been published in the Python Package Index (PyPI)</description></item><item><title>scikit-multiflow has been accepted at JMLR MLOSS!</title><link>https://scikit-multiflow.github.io/posts/2018-10-15-jmlr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scikit-multiflow.github.io/posts/2018-10-15-jmlr/</guid><description>The paper for &lt;a href="https://scikit-multiflow.github.io/">scikit-multiflow&lt;/a> has been accepted for publication at the &lt;em>Journal of Machine Learning Research - Machine Learning Open Source Software&lt;/em></description></item><item><title>About scikit-multiflow</title><link>https://scikit-multiflow.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scikit-multiflow.github.io/about/</guid><description>scikit-multiflow is an open-source machine learning package for streaming data. It extends the scientific tools available in the Python ecosystem. scikit-multiflow is intended for streaming data applications where data is continuously generated and must be processed and analyzed on the go. Data samples are not stored, so learning methods are exposed to new data only once.
The (theoretical) infinite nature of data stream poses additional challenges to learning. Resources such as memory and time are limited, and stream learning methods must efficiently handle resources.</description></item><item><title>Citing scikit-multiflow</title><link>https://scikit-multiflow.github.io/citing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scikit-multiflow.github.io/citing/</guid><description>If scikit-multiflow has been useful for your research and you would like to cite it in a academic publication, please use the following Bibtex entry:
Scikit-Multiflow: A Multi-outputStreaming Framework. Jacob Montiel, Jesse Read, Albert Bifet, Talel Abdessalem; Journal of Machine Learning Research, 19(72):1−5, 2018 | Bibtex</description></item><item><title>Community</title><link>https://scikit-multiflow.github.io/community/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scikit-multiflow.github.io/community/</guid><description>User questions The following options are available to learn, teach and ask questions
Google group: scikit-multiflow users
Gitter channel: scikit-multiflow/community
Contributing As an open source project, we welcome contributions from the community. Please refer to the contributor’s page for further information.
GitHub issue tracker For development-related issues:
For bug reports (something not working as documented) Documentation issues (incomplete/incorrect information in the documentation) Feature requests (something that you can not do)</description></item></channel></rss>